Join our design systems event in SF on 6/26

Toggle Menu

Privacy Policy
--------------

#### 1\. Introduction

StackBlitz values your privacy. This Privacy Policy details important information regarding the use and disclosure of your information collected on stackblitz.com. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to StackBlitz’s Terms of Service. Your use of stackblitz.com and any personal information you provide on or through stackblitz.com remains subject to this Privacy Policy and StackBlitz’s Terms of Service.

Special Note to International Users. Stackblitz.com is hosted in the United States and is intended for and directed to users in the United States. If you are an user accessing stackblitz.com from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of stackblitz.com, which is governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Policy, and StackBlitz’s Terms of Service, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer.

#### 2\. Information StackBlitz Receives from You

You provide certain personally identifiable information (such as your name and email address) to StackBlitz when you register for an account or correspond with us. In addition, if you choose to purchase products or services from us, then StackBlitz will ask you for additional information including your credit card information and billing address. StackBlitz may also seek ask you for demographic information including your age, gender, preferences and interests.

#### 3\. Information StackBlitz Collects

Cookies Information. When you visit stackblitz.com, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. StackBlitz uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of stackblitz.com may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

Log File Information. When you use stackblitz.com, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

Clear Gifs Information. When you use stackblitz.com, we may employ “clear gifs” (a.k.a. Web Beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our Users anonymously (i.e., in a non-personally-identifiable manner). In addition, we may also use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our Users to track which emails are opened by recipients.

Third-Parties. StackBlitz may receive personally identifiable information about you from third parties, including, for example, information about your transactions, purchase history, or relationships with various product and service providers, and your use of certain applications. For example, if you access stackblitz.com through a third-party connection or log-in, for example, through Facebook Connect, by “following,” “liking,” linking your account to the stackblitz.com service that third party may pass certain information about your use of its service to StackBlitz. This information could include, but is not limited to, the user ID associated with your account, any information you have permitted the third party to share with us, and any information you have made public in connection with that service. You should always review, and if necessary, adjust your privacy settings on third-party websites and services before linking or connecting them to stackblitz.com.

Analytics Information: We use third-party analytics tools to help us measure traffic and usage trends for stackblitz.com. These tools collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, including the web pages you visit, your browser add-ons, your browser’s width and height, and other information that assists us in improving stackblitz.com and the products or services offered at stackblitz.com. We collect and use this analytics information in aggregate form such that it cannot reasonably be manipulated to identify any particular individual user.

#### 4\. The Way StackBlitz Uses Information

Contact its Users. We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major changes to stackblitz.com or for customer service purposes).

Improve Stackblitz.com. We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of stackblitz.com and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing our users’ preferences and trends. We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit stackblitz.com; (b) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; and (c) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.

#### 5\. When StackBlitz Discloses Information

Provide Services. We provide personally identifiable information and non-personally-identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our privacy policy, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

However, we do not share your personally identifiable information (such as name or email address) with other, third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.

We do share non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on stackblitz.com.

Legal Requests and Comply with State and Federal Laws. We may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright Law) or respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant.

StackBlitz also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information that StackBlitz believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms of Service, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of stackblitz.com.

In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy. In the event that StackBlitz is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.

Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites. StackBlitz may allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within stackblitz.com. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the stackblitz.com. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens.

These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. StackBlitz does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks. StackBlitz’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

#### 6\. Your Choices

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through stackblitz.com, in which case StackBlitz may not be able to provide certain services to you.

You may update or correct your personal profile information and email preferences at any time by visiting your account profile page.

#### 7\. Our Commitment To Data Security

StackBlitz uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to StackBlitz and stackblitz.com and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, StackBlitz makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

If StackBlitz learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. StackBlitz may post a notice on stackblitz.com if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify us at [](mailto:hello@stackblitz.com)[hello@stackblitz.com](mailto:hello@stackblitz.com).

#### 8\. Changes and updates to this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically and this will be reflected by the “effective date” below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, we only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Policy in effect when we received the personal information you provided. Your continued use of stackblitz.com constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any future revisions.

For revisions to this Privacy Policy that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of the personal information you have already provided to us, we will attempt to obtain your consent before implementing such revisions with respect to such information.

#### 9\. How to Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or stackblitz.com, please contact us at [](mailto:hello@stackblitz.com)[hello@stackblitz.com](mailto:hello@stackblitz.com) or 2443 Fillmore St #380-7122, San Fransisco, CA 94115.

Effective Date: July 20, 2017

Products

Platform

Support

Company

StackBlitz Codeflow and the Infinite Pull Request logo are trademarks of StackBlitz, Inc.

© 2024 StackBlitz, Inc.
